<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
  id="skin.rapier"
  version="pre-4.2.0"
  name="Rapier"
  provider-name="Scarfa">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="3.00"/>
    <import addon="script.favourites" version="3.2.1"/>
    <import addon="script.artwork.downloader" version="1.0.1"/>
  </requires>
  <extension 
    point="xbmc.gui.skin"
    defaultthemename="textures.xbt" 
    effectslowdown="0.75"
    debugging="false"/>
    <res width="1280" height="720" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="720p"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">Rapier skin by Scarfa.</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Rapier autorstwa Scarfa.</summary>
	<summary lang="el">Rapier από τον Scarfa.</summary>
    <description lang="en">The goal is to provide a simple to use but clean and elegant interface that focuses on efficiency when browsing your media. Important considerations are put on usability, performance, and providing the user with flexibility when it comes to customization. Rapier tries to support all the latest features XBMC has to offer as long as it fits in with the skin's design goals.</description>
    <description lang="pl">Celem jest dostarczenie prostego w użyciu, a jednocześnie przejrzystego i eleganckiego interfejsu, wydajnego podczas przeglądania mediów. Szczególny nacisk położono na użyteczność, wydajność oraz zapewnienie użytkownikowi elastyczności w jej konfiguracji. Rapier stara się obsługiwać wszystkie najnowsze funkcje, jakie XBMC ma do zaoferowania, tak długo, jak pasują one do celów projektowych skóry.</description>
    <description lang="el">Στόχος είναι η παροχή ενός απλού στη χρήση, καθαρού και κομψού περιβάλλοντος που εστιάζει στην απόδοση κατά την περιήγηση των πολυμέσων σας. Έχει δοθεί έμφαση στην χρηστικότητα, στην απόδοση, και στην παροχή στο χρήστη ευέλικτων δυνατοτήτων προσαρμογής. Το Rapier προσπαθεί να υποστηρίξει όλες τις τελευταίες δυνατότητες που προσφέρει το XBMC, αρκεί να ταιριάζουν με τους στόχους του σχεδιασμού του.</description>
    <disclaimer></disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
